## **Christopher Yarbrough**

(720) 372-6252

christopher.e.yarbrough@gmail.com

## Summary

Dedicated IT Professional with 4 years of experience with a wide range of disciplines. Adept at network support, hardware troubleshooting and a strong background in customer service. Strong technical acumen, and a tech geek at heart. Trainer and leader. Able to grasp new concepts quickly and efficiently.

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages: C++, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3

Operating Systems: Windows: 7 - 10. Linux: RHEL 7, Ubuntu. Macintosh OS

Other: DHCP, Active Directory, Wordpress, Adobe Photoshop

#### Certifications

CompTIA: A+

### **Certifications Pursuing**

CompTIA: Network+, Linux+, Security+, Project+

Cisco: CCNA R&S, CCNA Security

Amazon: AWS Certified SysOp Administrator Associate

## **Experience**

CSRA Inc. March 2016 - Present

Network Support Technician

Responsible for imaging, installing and supporting hardware and software for workstations and laptops for Drug Enforcement Administration field offices. Providing IT support to all DEA offices during installation, and all Denver Division offices with 600+ users while not on travel. This position requires working knowledge of Active Directory, DHCP and all aspects of the Windows 7 Operating System. This is a client-facing role where desktop and network support are also prevalent. This role requires an active Secret clearance.

#### Syndicated Services Inc.

August 2013 - April 2016

Information Technology Specialist

Responsible for supporting all IT operations in the company, spread over several regions. Directly assisting agents, and executive leaders with desktop and advanced technical support, including management and development within Zoho Creator.

# North Carolina Army National Guard Specialist

February 2012 - December 2015

Responsible for operating, maintaining and training new soldiers on all vehicles, including max capacity vehicles that transport up to 20+ tons. This was a leadership position for which I was responsible for new soldiers that were assigned to our unit, and this included a significant amount of training.

## **Town of Troutman Planning**

December 2011 -

June 2012 GIS Intern

Participated in an internship with the Planning Department within the Town of Troutman at Town Hall. Worked in tandem with one other intern creating zoning and topographical maps using ArcGIS Desktop. These maps are still in use by the Planning Department.

#### Education

Western Governors University - B.S. Information Technology Expected December 2017

References provided upon request.